

# Nikolaiev Mykhailo

Full Stack developer

O Ukraine, Kyiv

☑ ab3mn3@gmail.com

**%** +38-066-800-79-85

#### SOCIAL

in in/mykhailo-nikolaiev

C) ab3MN

</>
Codewars

## EDUCATION

Thermal power engineer Kyiv energy college

2006-2010

Thermal power engineer

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute 2014-2018

#### SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML

TypeScript

· css/scss

• React/Redux

Nodejs(Express)

GIT

• MongoDB/mongoose

# SOFT SKILLS

Analytical

Communicative

Proactive

Innovative

Self-startina

Creative

Detailed

Adaptable

#### PROFILE

Courteous and enthusiastic, I am interested in IT. I recently began to be fascinated by web programming, e.g. developing apps and building websites. I am keen to gain more experience in the field. For this reason, I am looking for a company willing to offer me a placement among their developers. In return, I would offer my full commitment, and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team. I am therefore currently looking for a job or an internship as a front-end developer. My objective is to become a middle within one years.

# **EXPERIENCE**

Warehouse manager

From 2021 to Present | PLV SYSTEMS

Storekeeper

From 2018 to 2019 | Kasta

Mechanic engineer of machine manufacturer

From 2014 to 2018 | Kyiv Electric Train Repair Plant

#### PORTFOLIO

Plv:React/TypeScript/SCSS/responsive

Pet:React/TypeScript/Redux/SCCS/Express/MongoDB/mongoose

BackEnd:Express/MongoDB/mongoose/Cyclic

Travel: React/TypeScript/Adeptive Design

Pet: React/Redux/TypeScript/AJAX

CV: Adeptive Design(html,css,js)

## LANGUAGES

Ukraine

Russian

• English(Intermediate)

# INTERESTS

1 Music

× Travel

Rook

(H) Gym

ů

Study

广 Walk